[{"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07070", "answers": [{"answer": "twice many as", "id": "y4vnm", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as twice many", "id": "jTyj4", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as many twice", "id": "Wkj4C", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "6crfe", "text": "twice as many", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "p61LX", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.892Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07070", "question": "(Đề Thi THPT Quốc Gia 2015 – Mã Đề 194) After the new technique had been introduced, the factory produced ______ cars in 2014 as the year before.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.407Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07072", "answers": [{"answer": "more", "id": "zhCJi", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "most", "id": "ogCSg", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more", "id": "ZFlPP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "37it", "text": "the most", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "xsG5a", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.915Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07072", "question": "(Đề Thi Minh Họa THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Lần thứ nhất) The more demanding the job is, ______ I like it.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.435Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07074", "answers": [{"answer": "more and more", "id": "gIgoG", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more and the more", "id": "A2etJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most and the most", "id": "7ychv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3gh80", "text": "most and most", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "ALgi0", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.922Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07074", "question": "(Đề Thi Minh Họa THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Lần thứ 2) Air pollution is getting ______ serious in big cities in the world.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.445Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07076", "answers": [{"answer": "the better results he gets", "id": "34JcX", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "his results get better", "id": "8MawH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the better do his results get", "id": "Pi0gP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "7kcmi", "text": "the best results he gets", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "kiUm4", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.926Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07076", "question": "(Đề Thi Minh Họa THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Lần thứ 3) The harder he studies, ______.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.457Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07078", "answers": [{"answer": "the most crowded the beaches get", "id": "hx8cX", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most the beaches get crowded", "id": "T4Wi0", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more crowded the beaches get", "id": "ODTQd", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3uk33", "text": "the more the beaches get crowded", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "SLdWs", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.930Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07078", "question": "(Đề Thi THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Mã đề 401) The better the weather is, ______.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.470Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0707a", "answers": [{"answer": "the more fluently you can speak it", "id": "BLIlp", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more fluent you can speak it", "id": "g0ZQD", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more you can speak it fluent", "id": "dPDf9", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3v8p8", "text": "the more you can speak it fluently", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "c0XYn", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.933Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0707a", "question": "(Đề Thi THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Mã đề 402) The more you practise speaking English, ______.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.480Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0707c", "answers": [{"answer": "the most frequent natural disasters are", "id": "swERQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most frequently natural disasters occur", "id": "mqaHY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more frequent are natural disasters", "id": "2ZvW9", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "b38m", "text": "the more frequently natural disasters occur", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "tk4RY", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.939Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0707c", "question": "(Đề Thi THPT Quốc Gia 2017 – Mã đề 403) The larger the area of forest is destroyed, ______.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.490Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0707e", "answers": [{"answer": "more comfortable", "id": "Belzb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "comfortabler", "id": "zmhIH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most comfortable", "id": "XZwZ6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8i77u", "text": "comfortable", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "2n6vd", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.944Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0707e", "question": "This chair is………………… than that chair (comfortable)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.501Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07080", "answers": [{"answer": "more large", "id": "oXUEl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more larger", "id": "jPnLT", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "larger", "id": "ZD97N", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "dfppe", "text": "large", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "KFH2s", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.950Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07080", "question": "Your flat is…………………..than mine ( large)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.511Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07082", "answers": [{"answer": "prettier", "id": "qlGPu", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more pretty", "id": "Dk5I6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more prettier", "id": "5JbwQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "5v80s", "text": "prettier than", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "zaNoB", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.957Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07082", "question": "This dress is…………………..than that one (pretty)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.524Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07084", "answers": [{"answer": "important than", "id": "YxlQR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more important", "id": "mXbvG", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most important", "id": "KILXn", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "b0c0c", "text": "as important as", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "W2iCJ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.961Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07084", "question": "Albert Einstein’s contributions to scientific theory were ................ those of Galileo and Newton.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.531Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07086", "answers": [{"answer": "faster than", "id": "uloWH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "fast as", "id": "t6lw4", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "fast", "id": "ipsJ9", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "4ulc0", "text": "are fast as", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "VuNYH", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.964Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07086", "question": "Impalas cannot move as ................ cheetahs but they are more efficient runners.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.538Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07088", "answers": [{"answer": "best", "id": "Wdfsq", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the best", "id": "61x1F", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "most", "id": "Kpj8f", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "be9s4", "text": "better", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "g9NRn", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.968Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07088", "question": "Both are informative articles, but this one is ................ .", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.546Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0708a", "answers": [{"answer": "more beautiful", "id": "W0Z1L", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "beauty", "id": "bhJk3", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "most beautiful", "id": "YkUIk", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "9a4ic", "text": "more beautifully", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "m27r4", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.973Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0708a", "question": "She is the .…………  girl in our town.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.554Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0708c", "answers": [{"answer": "The better is your English", "id": "pbhvx", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The better will be your English", "id": "DuX6v", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The better becomes your English", "id": "nmziM", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "alftt", "text": "The better your English will be", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "RyP93", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.978Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0708c", "question": "The harder you learn.............", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.564Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b0708e", "answers": [{"answer": "clever", "id": "44TJj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "cleverest", "id": "HjHWu", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "cleverer", "id": "fljnF", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "7eacd", "text": "more clever", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "qkeHE", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.982Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b0708e", "question": "Jim is the ................. in his class.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.571Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07090", "answers": [{"answer": "the prettiest", "id": "WPDAd", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the most pretty", "id": "7IWY7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "prettier", "id": "XVLMG", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3he36", "text": "the prettier", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "edrpi", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.987Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07090", "question": "Of the two shirts, this one is ...................", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.578Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07092", "answers": [{"answer": "as bigger as", "id": "6FSib", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "many times as big as", "id": "2tlnG", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "much big as", "id": "Xs4hQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2psej", "text": "not many times big", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "MHven", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.990Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07092", "question": "Your house is ................. mine.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.586Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07094", "answers": [{"answer": "This year it is as colder than last year.", "id": "44nSW", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "This year it  is colder than last year.", "id": "ojxw2", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "This year it isn’t as cold as last year.", "id": "RNTGE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3vjfp", "text": "This year it isn’t colder than last year.", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "bMaZx", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.994Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07094", "question": "Last year it wasn’t as cold as this year.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.593Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5977159a6072386304b07096", "answers": [{"answer": "I’m more younger than her.", "id": "yQPQZ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "I’m as younger as her.", "id": "H7R3z", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "fbl5o", "text": "I’m more young than her.", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "Rahsd", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "j12c", "text": "I’m younger than her.  ", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "question1500976370760", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-25T09:55:38.998Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5977159a6072386304b07096", "question": "She is older than me.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-01T02:58:02.599Z"}]